Finding Aid for the Republic Pictures Corporation Records LSC.0979
UCLA Library Special Collections
Republic Pictures Corporation records
1935-1960
UCLA Library Special Collections
Republic Pictures Corporation
LSC.0979
69.5 linear feet (139 boxes)
Republic Pictures Corporation was created in 1935 by merging four minor studios. The studio produced mostly westerns in assembly-line fashion, and occasionally produced a major motion picture under direction of Raoul Walsh, John Ford, or Orson Welles. The collection consists of shooting and continuity scripts for approximately 2000 titles.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Materials without or with ambiguous box numbers, e.g. * or -, are currently not accessible.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of David Bloom, 1967.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9927230663606533
Biography
Republic Pictures Corporation was created in 1935; formed by Herbert J. Yates, owner of a film laboratory, by merging four minor studios; created B movies, producing mostly westerns, in assembly-line fashion; occasionally produced a major motion picture under direction of Raoul Walsh, John Ford, or Orson Welles; as B movies were eliminated in the 1950s, Republic abandoned film production in favor of television programming; Yates retired in 1959.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of shooting and continuity scripts for approximately 2000 titles. Includes Gene Autry, John Wayne, and Roy Rogers movies as well as Orson Welles' Macbeth.
Portions of this collection are available in duplicated or original form at the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences, the British Film Institute, the Museum of Modern Art (New York, New York), and at the University of Southern California.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Continuity scripts (Boxes 1-61).
Shooting scripts (Boxes 62-139).
Film scripts.; Motion picture industry -- Archives.; Republic Pictures Corporation -- Archives
- Continuity Scripts
  - The Red Menace, 1949.; 7 copies (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Director: R.G. Springsteen
    Cast: Robert Rockwell, Hanne Axman, Betty Lou Gerson
  - My Best Gal., 1944.; 5 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: Anthony Mann
    Cast: Jane Withers, Jimmy Lydon
  - Hearts in Bondage., 1936.; 5 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: Lew Ayres
    Cast: James Dunn, Mae Clark, David Manners
  - Diary of a Bride., 1948.; 9 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: John H. Auer
    Cast: Ruth Hussy, John Carroll, Vera Ralston, Gene Lockhart
  - Dark Violence., 1948.; 10 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: Allan Dwan and Philip Ford
    Cast: John Carroll, Adele Mara, Thomas Gomez
  - Goodnight Sweetheart (Box 1)
  - Pride of the Navy., 1939.; 8 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: Charles Lamont
    Cast: James Funn, Rochelle Hudson, Gordon Oliver
  - Lonely Heart Bandits., 1950.; 5 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: George Blair
    Cast: Dorothy Patrick, John Eldredge, Barbra Fuller
  - Daughter of the Jungle., 1949.; 10 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: George Blair (Lois Hall, James Cardwell = east)
  - Million Dollar Pursuit., 1951.; 10 copies. (Box 1)
    Cast: Penny Edwards, Grant Withers
  - A Woman's Devotion., 1956.; 10 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: Paul Henried
    Cast: Ralph Meeker, Janice Rule, Paul Henried
  - Bullfighter and the Lady (domestic)., 1951.; 2 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: Budd Boetticher
    Cast: Robert Stack, Joy Page, Gilbert Roland, Katy Jurado
  - The Madonna's Secret., 1946.; 10 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: William Thiele
    Cast: Francis Lederer, Gail Patrick, Ann Rutherford
  - Swingin' On a Rainbow., 1945.; 4 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: William Beaudine
    Cast: Jane Frazee, Brad Taylor
  - The Tiger Man., 1944.; 9 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: George Sherman
    Cast: Erich von Stroheim, Vera Ralston, Richard Arlen
  - Tobor the Great., 1954.; 9 copies. (Box 1)
    Director: Lee Sholem
    Cast: Charles Drake, Karin Booth, Billy Chapin
  - Marshal Of Cedar Rock., 1952.; 10 copies. (Box 2)
    Director: Harry Keller
    Cast: Eddy Waller, Allan Lane, Phyllis Coates, Roy Barcroft
  - The Old Frontier., 1950.; 9 copies. (Box 2)
    Director: Philip Ford
    Cast: Monte Hale, Paul Hurst, Claudia Barrett
  - Hellfire., 1949.; 10 copies. (Box 2)
    Cast: Marie Windsor, Forrest Tucker, Jim Davis, H.B. Warner
  - Road to Alcatraz., 1945.; [Duplicate]. (Box 2)
    Director: Nick Grinde
    Cast: Robert Lowery, June Storey, Grant Withers, Clarence Colb
    - Road to Alcatraz. (trailer)., 1945; 20 copies.
  - Lone Texas Ranger., 1945.; 14 copies. (Box 2)
    Director: Spencer Bennet
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, Bobby Blake, Alice Fleming
  - The Missourians., 1950.; 3 copies. (Box 2)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Paul Hurst, Roy Barcroft, Lyn Thomas
  - The Doolin Gang and Little Britches (Stories of the Century)., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 2)
    Director: William Witney
    Cast: Jim Davis, Mary Castle, Leo Gordon
  - Tom Horn and Black Jack Ketchum., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 2)
    Cast: Jim Davis, Mary Castle
  - Redwood Forest Trail., 6 copies. (Box 2)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Jeff Donnell, Jane Darwell, Carl alfalfa Switzer
  - Mojave Firebrand., 1944.; 14 copies. (Box 2)
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, George 'Gabby' Hayes
  - Great Stagecoach Robbery., 1945.; 5 copies. (Box 2)
    Director: Lesley Selander
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, Bobby Blake
  - Powder River Rustlers., 1950.; 9 copies. (Box 2)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Gerry Ganz, Roy Barcroft
  - Prairie Moon., 1938.; 10 copies. (Box 2)
    Director: Ralph Staub
    Cast: Gene Autry
  - Savage Frontier., 1953.; 10 copies. (Box 2)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Bob Steele, Dorothy Patrick
  - Marshal of Cripple Creek., 1947.; 6 copies. (Box 2)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Bobby Lane, Martha Wentworth, William Self
  - Woman in the Dark., 1951.; 10 copies. (Box 3)
    Cast: Penny Edwards, Ross Elliott
  - The Eternal Sea., 1955.; 6 copies. (Box 3)
    Cast: Sterling Hayden, Alexis Smith, Dean Jagger, Ben Cooper
    - The Eternal Sea. (trailer)., 1955; 4 copies.
  - The Mysterious Miss X., 1939.; 1 copy. (Box 3)
    Director: Gus Meins
    Cast: Michael Whalen, Mary Hart, Regis Toomey
  - Tell it to a Star., 1945.; 4 copies. (Box 3)
    Director: Frank McDonald
    Cast: Ruth Terry, Robert Livingston
  - The Pretender., 1947.; 11 copies. (Box 3)
    Director: W. Lee Wilder
    Cast: Albert Dekker, Catherine Craig, Charles Drake, Allan Carney
  - Missile Monsters., 1950.; 4 copies. (Box 3)
    Director: Fred. C. Brannon
    Cast: Walter Reed, Lois Collier
  - Tropical Heat Wave., 1952.; 10 copies. (Box 3)
    Cast: Estelita, Robert Hutton
    - Tropical Heat Wave. (trailer)., 1952; 23 copies.
  - Hi, Neighbor., 1942.; 11 copies. (Box 3)
    Director: Charles LaMont
    Cast: Jean Parker, John Areher, Marilyn Hare, Vera Vague
  - A Strange Adventure., 1956.; 11 copies. (Box 3)
    Cast: Joan Evans, Ben Cooper, Nick Adams
    - A Strange Adventure. (trailer)., 1956; 27 copies.
  - Youth on Parade., 1942.; 9 copies. (Box 3)
    Director: Albert S. Rogell
    Cast: John Hubbard, Ruth Terry, Martha O'Driscoll
  - Hitchhike to Happiness., 1944.; 10 copies. (Box 3)
    Director: Joseph Santley
    Cast: Al Pearce, Dale Evans, Brad Taylor, William Frawley
  - The Lady Wants Mink., 1952.; 9 copies. (Box 3)
    Director: William A. Seiter
    Cast: Dennis O'Keefe, Ruth Hussey, Eve Arden, William Demarest
  - Sing, Neighbor, Sing., 1944.; 3 copies. (Box 3)
    Cast: Roy Acuff, Rachel, Lulubelle and Scotty, Brad Taylor
  - O.S.S. 117 Is Not Dead; O.S.S. 117 N'est Pas Mort., 1957.; [Duplicate].; 21 copies. (Box 4)
    Director: Jean Sacha
    Cast: Magali Noel, Ivan Desny, Yves Vincent
  - Casanova in Burlesque., 1943.; 4 copies. (Box 4)
    Director: Leslie Goodwins
    Cast: Joe E. Brown, June Havoc, Dale Evans, Lucien Littlefield
  - No Place to Land., 1958.; 8 copies. (Box 4)
    Director: Albert C. Gunnaway
    Cast: John Ireland, Mari Blanchard, Gail Russell, Jackie Coogan
  - Robinson Crusoe of Clipper Island., 1936.; 3 copies. (Box 4)
    Director: Mack V. Wright, Ray Taylor
    Cast: Mala, Rex, Buck, Mamo Clark, Herbert Rawlinson, William Newell
  - The Girl from Alaska., 1942.; 15 copies. (Box 4)
    Cast: Ray Middleton, Jean Parker, Jerome Cowan, Robert H. Barrat
  - Terror at Midnight., 1956.; 10 copies. (Box 4)
    Director: Franklin Andreon
    Cast: Scott Brady, Joan Vohs, Frank Faylen
  - Heart of Virginia., 1948.; 5 copies. (Box 4)
    Cast: Janet Martin, Robert Lowery, Frankie Darro, Paul Hurst
  - Three Little Sisters., 1944.; 8 copies. (Box 4)
    Cast: Mary Lee, Ruth Terry, Cheryl Walker, William Terry
  - The Notorious Mr. Monks., 1958.; 2 copies. (Box 4)
    Director: Joe Kane
    Cast: Vera Ralsoon, Don Kelly, Paul Fix
  - Road to Alcatraz., 1945.; 10 copies. (Box 4)
    Cast: Robert Lowery, June Storey, Grant Withers
  - Rodeo King and the Señorita., 1951.; 2 copies. (Box 5)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Mary Ellen Kay, Buddy Ebsen, Roy Bargroft
    - Rodeo King and the Señorita. (trailer)., 1951; 8 copies.
  - Pawnee., 1957.; 2 copies. (Box 5)
    Director: George Waggner
    Cast: George Montgomery, Bill Williams, Lola Albright
  - Salt Lake Raiders., 1950.; 3 copies. (Box 5)
    Director: Fred C. Brannon
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller
  - Rio Grande Raiders., 1946.; 12 copies. (Box 5)
    Director: Thomas Carr
    Cast: Sunset Carson, Linda Stirling, Bob Steele, Tom London
  - California Outpost., 1948.; 1 copy. (Box 5)
    Cast: William Elliott, John Carroll, Catherine McLeod
  - The Laramie Trail., 1944.; 7 copies. (Box 5)
    Director: John English
    Cast: Bob Livingston, Smiley Burnette, Linda Brent
  - Ridin' the Long Trail., 1 copy. (Box 5)
    Director: Sam Newfield
    Cast: Bob Steele, Claire Rochelle, Charles King, Ernie Adams
  - Prince of the Plains., 1949.; 9 copies. (Box 5)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Paul Hurst
  - Roarin' Lead., 1936.; 1 copy. (Box 5)
    Director: Mack V. Wright, Sam Newfield
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Ray Corrigan, Max Terhune, Christine Maple, Tommy Bupp
  - Renegades of Sonora., 1948.; 2 copies. (Box 5)
    Cast: Allan Rocky Lane Eddy Waller
  - Riders of the Black Hills., 1938.; 4 copies. (Box 5)
    Cast: Robert Livingsto, Ray Corrigan
  - Ride That Man Down. trailer (20)., 1952; 3 copies. (Box 5)
    Director: Joseph Kane
    Cast: Brian Donlevy, Rod Cameron
  - Riders of the Whistling Skull., 1936.; 5 copies. (Box 5)
    Director: Mack V. Wright
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Ray Corrigan
  - Riders of the Rio Grande., 1943.; 3 copies. (Box 5)
    Director: Howard Bretherton
    Cast: Bob Steele, Tom Tyler, Jimmie Dodd
  - Rhythm Hits the Ice., 1946.; 5 copies. (Box 6)
    Director: Bernard Vorhaus
    Cast: Ellen Drew, Richard Denning Jerry Colonna
  - The Man Who Died Twice., 1958.; 3 copies. (Box 6)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Vera Ralston, Mike Mazurki
  - Public Enemies., 1941.; 3 copies. (Box 6)
    Cast: Phillip Terry, Wendy Barrie, Edgar Kennedy, William Frawley
  - The Port of Forty Thieves., 1944.; 7 copies. (Box 6)
    Cast: Stephanie Bachelor, Richard Powers, Lynn Roberts
  - In Old Oklahoma., 1943.; 2 copies. (Box 6)
    Cast: John Wayne, Martha Scott
  - The Fabulous Suzanne., 1946.; 17 copies. (Box 6)
    Director: Steve Sekely
    Cast: Barbara Britton, Rudy Vallee, Otto Kruger, Richard Denning
  - Escape by Night., 1937.; 2 copies. (Box 6)
    Director: Hamilton MacFadden
    Cast: William Hall, Anne Nagel, Dean Jagger, Ward Bond
  - Puddin' Head., 1941.; 4 copies. (Box 6)
    Director: Joseph Sintley
    Cast: Francis Lederer, Raymond Walburn, Slim Summerville, Astrid Allwym
  - Music in the Moonlight., 1941.; 11 copies. (Box 6)
    Director: Joseph Stantley
    Cast: Dorothy Lewis, James Ellison, Jerry Colonna
  - Moonrise., 1948.; 6 copies. (Box 6)
    Director: Frank Borzage
    Cast: Dane Clark, Gail Russell, Ethel Barrymore
  - Outcasts of the City., 1956.; 2 copies. (Box 6)
    Director: Boris L. Petroff
    Cast: Osa Massen, Robert Hutton, Maria Palmer
  - Portia on Trial., 1937.; 5 copies. (Box 6)
    Director: George Nicholls, Jr.
    Cast: Walter Abel, Frieda Inescort, Neil Hamilton, Heather Angel
  - Man from Frisco., 1944.; 7 copies. (Box 7)
    Director: Robert Florey
    Cast: Gene Lockhart, Michael O'Shea, Anne Shirley, Dan Duryea
  - Man of Conquest., 1939.; 2 copies. (Box 7)
    Director: George Nicholls Jr.
    Cast: Richard Dix, Gail Patrick Edward Ellis, Joan Fontaine
  - The Last Crooked Mile., 1946.; 4 copies. (Box 7)
    Cast: Donald Barry, Ann Savage, Adele Mara, Tom Powers
  - Exposed., 1947.; 7 copies. (Box 7)
    Cast: Adele Mara, Robert Scott, Adrian Booth, Robert Armstrong
  - Laughing Anne., 1953.; 9 copies. (Box 7)
    Director: Herbert Wilcox
    Cast: Wendell Corey, Margaret Lockwood, Forest Tucker, Ronald Shiner
  - London Blackout Murders., 1942.; 1 copy. (Box 7)
    Cast: John Abbott, Mary McLeod, Lloyd Corrigan, Lester Matthews
  - Madonna of the Desert., 1948.; 15 copies. (Box 7)
    Cast: Lynne Roberts, Donald Barry, Don Castle
  - Girls of the Big House., 1945.; 7 copies. (Box 7)
    Director: George Archainbaud
    Cast: Lynne Roberts, Virginia Christine, Marian Martin
  - The Girl from Mandalay., 1936.; 6 copies. (Box 7)
    Director: Howard Brotherton
    Cast: Conrad Nagel, Kay Linaker, Donald Cook
  - Rhythm In The Clouds., 1937.; 2 copies. (Box 7)
    Cast: Patricia Ellis, Warren Hull, William Newell
  - Girl from God's Country., 1940.; 8 copies. (Box 7)
    Director: Sidney Salkow
    Cast: Mala, Kate Lawson, John Bleifer
  - The Return of Jimmy Valentine., 1936.; 7 copies. (Box 7)
    Director: Lewis D. Collins
    Cast: Roger Pryer, Charlotte Henry
  - The Girl Who Dared., 1944.; 5 copies. (Box 7)
    Cast: Lorna Gray, Peter Cookson
  - Lost Planet Airmen., 1949.; 1 copy. (Box 7)
    Cast: Tristram Coffin, Mae Clarke, Don Haggerty, House Peters, Jr.
  - Utah Wagon Train., 1951.; 2 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Penny Edwards, Buddy Ebsen
  - Utah Wagon Train., 1951.; 11 copies. (Box 8)
    Director: John K. Butler
    Cast: Rex Allen, KoKo
  - The Vanishing Westerner. (trailer)., 1950; 10 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Paul Hurst, Aline Towne
  - Vigilantes of Boomtown., 1946.; 4 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Allen Lane, Bobby Blake, Martha Wentworth
  - The Vanishing American., 1955.; 2 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Scott Brady, Audrey Totter
  - Last Frontier Uprising., 1946.; 6 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Monte Hae, Adrian Booth, James Taggart, Rpy Barcroft
  - Last Stagecoach West., 1957.; 3 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Jim Davis, Mary Castle, Victor Jory
  - Law of the Golden West., 1949.; 13 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Paul Hurst, Gail Davis, Roy Barcroft
  - The Lawless Eighties., 1957.; 2 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Buster Crabbe, John Smith, Marilyn Saris, Ted de Corsia
  - Lone Star Raiders., 1940.; 3 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Robert Livngston, Bob Steele Rufe Davis
  - Ghost of Zorro., 1959.; 3 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Clayton Moore, Pamola Blake
  - Pioneer Marshal., 1950.; 8 copies. (Box 8)
  - The Phantom Plainsmen., 1942.; 7 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Bob Steele, Tom Tyler
  - Wagon Tracks West., 1943.; 2 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, Gabby Hayes, Anne Jeffreys
  - San Antone Ambush., 1949.; 2 copies. (Box 8)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Bette Daniels, Paul Hurst
  - The Undercover Woman., 1946.; 4 copies. (Box 9)
    Cast: Stephanie Bachelor, Robert Livingston
  - The Zero Hour., 1939.; 1 copy. (Box 9)
    Cast: Frieda Inescort, Otto Kruger
  - Timberjack., 1950.; 1 copy. (Box 9)
    Cast: Sterling Hayden, Vera Ralston, David Brian, Adolphe Manjou
  - The Gambling Terror., 14 copies. (Box 9)
    Cast: Johnny Mack Brown, Iris Meredith Charlie King
  - Panama Sal., 1957.; 8 copies. (Box 9)
    Cast: Elena Verdugo, Edward Kemmer, Carlos Rivas, Harry Jackson
  - Tough Girl (re-edited from That Brennan Girl)., 1946.; 13 copies. (Box 9)
    Director: Alfred Santell
    Cast: James Dunn, Mona Freeman, William Marshal
    - Tough Girl (re-edited from That Brennan Girl). (trailer)., 1946; 23 copies.
  - A Man Betrayed., 1941.; 2 copies. (Box 9)
    Cast: John Wayne, Frances Dee, Edward Ellis, Wallace Ford
  - The Magnificent Rogue., 1947.; 2 copies. (Box 9)
    Cast: Lynne Roberts, Warren Douglas
  - Magic Fire., 1955.; 2 copies. (Box 9)
    Director: William Dieterle
    Cast: Yvonne De Carlo, Carlos Thompson, Allan Badel
  - Sea Racketeers., 1937.; 4 copies. (Box 9)
    Cast: Weldon Heyburn, Jeanne Madden, Warren Eymer
  - Unmasked., 1950.; 7 copies. (Box 9)
    Cast: Robert Rockwell, Barbra Fuller
  - Untamed Heiress., 1954.; 1 copy. (Box 9)
    Cast: Judy Canova, Donald Barry
  - Valley of Hunted Men., 1942.; 3 copies. (Box 9)
  - Valley of Hunted Men., 1942.; 3 copies. (Box 9)
  - The Old Frontier., 1950.; 3 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Claudia Barrett, William Henry
    - The Old Frontier. (trailer)., 1950; 9 copies.
  - Oklahoma Badlands., 1948.; 4 copies. (Box 10)
    Director: Yakima Canutt
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Mildred Coles
    - Oklahoma Badlands. (trailer)., 1948; 3 copies.
  - The Laramie Trail., 1944.; 3 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Bob Livingston, Smiley Burnette
  - Prince of the Plains., 1949.; 7 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Paul Hurst, Shirley Davis, Roy Barcroft
  - Quantrill and His Raiders and Beale Starr., 1954.; 9 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Jim Davis, Mary Castle, Marie Windsor, Bruce Bennett
    - Quantrill and His Raiders and Beale Starr. (trailer)., 1954; 2 copies.
  - Gangs of Sonora., 1941.; 5 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Bob Steele, Rufe Davis
  - Marshal of Cedar Rock., 1952.; 3 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Phyllis Coates
    - Marshal of Cedar Rock. (trailer)., 1952; 14 copies.
  - Plunderers of Painted Flats., 1958.; 7 copies. (Box 10)
    Director: Albert C. Gannaway
    Cast: Corinne Calvet, John Carroll, Skip Homeier, George MacReady, Bea Benaderet, Madge Kennedy
  - Zorro Rides Again., 1937.; 12 copies. (Box 10)
    Director: William Witney John English
    Cast: John Carroll, Helen Christian
  - Raiders of Old California., 1957.; 3 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Jim Davis, Arleen Whelan, Faron Young
  - Santa Fe Scouts., 1943.; 4 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Bob Steele, Tom Tyler, Jimmie Dodd, Lois Collier
  - Santa Fe Saddlemates., 1945.; 5 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Sunset Carson, Linda Stirling, Olin Howlin
  - The Topeka Terror., 1945.; 9 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Linda Stirling, Earle Hodgins, Twinkle Watts
    - The Topeka Terror. (trailer)., 1945; 24 copies.
  - Marshal of Reno., 1944.; 7 copies. (Box 10)
    Director: Wallace Grissell
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, Gabby Hayes, Alice Fleming
  - Oklahoma Renegades., 1940.; 5 copies. (Box 10)
    Director: Nate Watt
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Raymond Hatton, Duncan Renaldo
  - Range Defenders., 1937.; 4 copies. (Box 10)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Ray Corrigan, Max Terhune, Eleanor Stewart
  - Missile Monsters., 1958.; 1 copy. (Box 11)
    Cast: Walter Reed, Lois Collier, Gregory Gay
  - Gallant Thoroughbred., 1943.; 17 copies. (Box 11)
    Director: Robert Siodmak
    Cast: Mabel Paige, John Craven, Dorothy Morris, Charles Dingle
  - Gangs of New York., 1938.; 6 copies. (Box 11)
    Director: James Cruze
    Cast: Charles Bickford, Ann Dvorak, Wynn Gibson, Harold Huber
  - Woman from Headquarters., 1950.; 1 copy. (Box 11)
    Cast: Virginia Huston, Robert Rockwell, Barbra Fuller
  - Mountain Rhythm., 1942.; 13 copies. (Box 11)
    Cast: Weaver Bros., Elviry, Lynn Merrick, Sally Payne
  - The Old Homestead., 1942.; 3 copies. (Box 11)
    Director: Frank MacDonald
    Cast: Dick Purcell, Jed Prouty, Anna Jeffreys, Maris Wrixon
  - The Maverick Queen., 1956.; 2 copies. (Box 11)
    Cast: Barbara Stanwyck, Barry Sullivan
  - Manhattan Merry-go-round., 1937.; 1 copy. (Box 11)
    Director: Charles F. Riesner
    Cast: Phil Regan, Leo Carillo, Ann Dvorak, Kay Thompson, Joe Di Maggio, Louis Prima, INTRODUCING GENE AUTRY
  - Meet the Boy Friend., 1937.; 5 copies. (Box 11)
    Director: Ralph Staub (sp.?)
    Cast: David Carlyle, Carol Hughes, Warren Hymer, Pert Kelton
  - The Last Crooked Mile., 1946.; 16 copies. (Box 11)
    Cast: Donald Barry, Ann Savage, Adele Mare, Tom Powers
  - Larceny on the Air., 1936.; 6 copies. (Box 11)
    Director: Irving Pichel
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Grave Bradley, Willard Robertson
  - Larceny On The Air. CUT, 1936.; 10 copies. (Box 11)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Grace Bradley
  - Lake Placid Serenade., 1944.; 2 copies. (Box 11)
    Cast: Vera Ralston, Eugene Pallette, Vera Vague, Robert Livingston
  - Gangs of Chicago., 1940.; 7 copies. (Box 11)
    Director: Arthur Lubin
    Cast: Lloyd Nolan, Barton MacLane, Lola Lane, Ray Middleton
  - Man with the Steel Whip (serial) episodes 1-10., 1954.; 1 ea. copies. (Box 12)
    Cast: Richard Simmons, Barbara Bestar, Dale Van Sickel
    - Man with the Steel Whip (serial) episodes 1-10. (trailer)., 1954; 9 copies.
  - Oregon Trail Scouts., 1947.; 1 copy. (Box 12)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Bobby Blake, Martha Wentworth
    - Oregon Trail Scouts. (trailer)., 1947; 7 copies.
  - Pals of the Pecos., 1941.; 1 copy. (Box 12)
    Director: Les Orlebeck
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Bob Steele, Rufe Davis, June Johnson
  - Toughest Man in Arizona., 1952.; 1 copy. (Box 12)
    Cast: Vaughn Monroo, Joan Leslie, Edgar Puchanan, Victor Jory
  - Oregon Trail., 1936.; 6 copies. (Box 12)
    Director: Scotty Pembroke
    Cast: John Wayne, Ann Rutherford, Joe Girard, Yakima Canutt
  - Marshal of Cripple Creek., 1947.; 4 copies. (Box 12)
  - Old Oklahoma Plains., 6 copies. (Box 12)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Slim Pickens, Elaine Edwards, Roy Barcroft
    - Trailer., 1952.; 18 copies.
  - Bandits of the West., 1953.; 10 copies. (Box 12)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Cathy Downs, Byron Foulger
    - Bandits of the West. (trailer)., 1953; 24 copies.
  - Overland Mail Robbery., 1943.; 5 copies. (Box 12)
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, Gabby Hayes, Anne Jeffreys, Alice Fleming
  - The Twinkle in God's Eye., 1955.; 10 copies. (Box 12)
    Cast: Mickey Rooney, Goleen Gray, Hugh O'Brian
  - The Avengers., 1950.; 8 copies. (Box 12)
    Cast: John Carrol, Adele Mara, Mona Maris, Fernando Lamas
  - Under Colorado Skies., 1947.; 8 copies. (Box 12)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Adrian Booth, Paul Hurst
  - Pals of the Saddle., 1938.; 2 copies. (Box 12)
    Cast: John Wayne, Ray Corrigan, Max Terhune, Doreen McKay
  - Track the Man Down., 1954.; 1 copy. (Box 13)
    Cast: Kent Taylor, Petula Clark, Walter Rilla
  - Traffic in Crime., 1946.; 2 copies. (Box 13)
    Director: Les Selander
    Cast: Kane Richmond, Adele Mara, Anne Nagel, Wilton Graff
  - Trial without Jury., 1950.; 2 copies. (Box 13)
    Cast: Robert Rockwell, Barbra Fuller, Kent Taylor, Audrey Long
  - One Frightened Night., 1935.; 5 copies. (Box 13)
    Director: Christy Cabanne
    Cast: Mary Carlisle, Arthur Hohl, Wally Ford, Regis Toomey, Hedda Hopper
  - One Exciting Week., 1946.; 5 copies. (Box 13)
    Cast: Al Pearce, Pinky Lee, Jerome Cowan, Shemp Howard
  - Angel on the Amazon., 1948.; 5 copies. (Box 13)
    Cast: George Brent, Vera Ralston, Brian Aherne, Constance Bennett
  - Bill and Coo., 1948.; 1 copy. (Box 13)
    Director: Dean Riesner
    Cast: Ken Murray, George Burton's Love Birds, Curlet Twiford's Jimmy the Crow
    - Bill and Coo. (trailer)., 1948; 33 copies.
    - Bill and Coo. (trailer - Spanish)., 1948; 40 copies.
    - Bill and Coo. (trailer - Potuguese)., 1948; 36 copies.
  - Mr. District Attorney in the Carter Case., 1942.; 10 copies. (Box 13)
    Cast: James Ellison, Virginia Gilmore, Paul Harvey
  - A Gentle Gangster., 1942.; 4 copies. (Box 13)
    Director: Phil Rosen